A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Manuscripts Department Correspondence [ante 1990] and Patron-Use Files (Box A28-7A through A29-17T)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Tenth Annual 1939-1940 (Box A28-18Q)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Eleventh Annual 1940-1941 (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Twelfth Annual 1941-1942 (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Thirteenth Annual 1942-1943 (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Fourteenth Annual 1943-1944 (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - Fifteenth Annual 1944-1945 (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - 16th & 17th Annual (Box A28-18R)
    - Report on Historical Collections - 18th Annual (Box A28-18R)
    - Reports - Annual Reports on Historical Collections - General (Box A28-18R)
    - Report to Librarian 1967 Dec. (Box A28-18R)
    - Research Projects - Colonial History (Box A28-18S)
    - Restrictions - Memoranda About (Box A28-18S)
    - R.S.V.P. - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (Box A28-18S)
    - Reviews and Lists (Box A28-18S)
    - Revolutionary Period Diaries (Box A28-18S)
    - Revolutionary War (Box A28-18S)
    - Revolutionary War in Virginia (Box A28-18S)
    - Reynolds, James (Box A28-18S)
    - Rice, Howard C. (Box A28-18S)
    - Richards, L. Adolph (Box A28-18S)
    - Richards, Gertrude R.B. (Box A28-18S)
    - Richardson, Eudora Ramsay (Box A28-18S)
    - Richmond News Leader (Box A28-18S)
    - Ricks, James Hoge (Box A28-18S)
    - Riddick Family (Box A28-18S)
    - Riggle, J.B. (Box A28-18S)
    - Riley, Edward M. (Box A28-18S)
    - Riley, Mrs. Melville / Riley, Melville T., Sr. (Box A28-18S)
    - Rind, William / Rind, James (Box A28-18S)
    - Ripley, Alexandra 1984-1989 (Box A28-18S)
    - Rives, Amelie (Box A28-18S)
    - Rives Family Papers (Box A28-18S)
    - Rives Papers (Box A28-18S)
    - Rives, William Cabell (Box A28-18S)
    - Roane, Spencer (Box A28-18S)
    - Roanoke (see also Stone; Moore, R.; Hanes, L.; Stokes; Hancock, J.) (Box A28-18S)
    - Roanoke College (Box A28-18S)
    - Roanoke Times (Box A28-18S)
    - Robbins, Edwin H. (Box A28-18S)
    - Roberts, E. Graham 1948-1952 (Box A28-18S)
    - Roberts, John Alexander (Box A28-18S)
    - Roberts, Joseph Kent (Box A28-18S)
    - Roberts, Ruby A. (Box A28-18S)
    - Robertson, Frances (Box A28-18S)
    - Robertson, A. Willis (Box A28-18S)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (Box A28-18T)
    - Robinson, W. Stitt (Box A28-18T)
    - Robinson, William H., Ltd. (Box A28-18T)
    - Rockbridge Maps (Box A28-18T)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box A28-18T)
    - Rodick, B.C. (Box A28-18T)
    - Roe, Edward Payson (Box A28-18T)
    - Rogers, Bruce (Box A28-18T)
    - Rogers, John C. (Box A28-18T)
    - Rogers, William Barton (Box A28-18T)
    - Rolfe Acknowledgements (Box A28-18T)
    - Rolfe, John (Box A28-18T)
    - Rolfe, John - Will (Box A28-18T)
    - Rolfe Manuscripts (Box A28-18T)
    - Romaine, Dr. Mason (Box A29-9A)
    - Rommel (Box A29-9A)
    - Rose, Robert (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosenbach Company (see also Fleming, John F.) (1939- ) (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosenberg, Dr. Ralph (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosenberger, Francis Coleman (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosenwald, Lessing (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosser (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosser, Barbara - Estate of 1984-1987 (Box A29-9A)
    - Rosser, Thomas Lafayette (Box A29-9A)
    - Rotunda (Box A29-9A)
    - Rotunda - restoration (see also University of Virginia - Restoration) (Box A29-9A)
    - Rotunda Restoration Fund - Payroll & Purchases (Box A29-9B)
    - Rouleau, Fred (Box A29-9B)
    - Rouse, Parke (Box A29-9B)
    - Rowson, Susanna H. (Box A29-9B)
    - Royall, Ann (Box A29-9B)
    - Royce, W.H. (Box A29-9B)
    - Rubin, Louis D. (Box A29-9B)
    - Rucker, Mrs. Walton (Box A29-9B)
    - Rudd, Hughes (Box A29-9B)
    - Rudge (Box A29-9B)
    - R.S.V.P. (Box A29-9B)
    - Ruffner, Alvin F. (Box A29-9B)
    - Ruffner, J.P. (Box A29-9B)
    - Ruffner, William Henry (Box A29-9B)
    - Rules and Regulations - for the use of manuscripts (Box A29-9B)
    - Rumbough, Constance (Box A29-9B)
    - Rummel, Richard (Box A29-9B)
    - Rumsey, James (see also Washington, George; Sydnor, Mrs. Garland) (Box A29-9B)
    - Runk, B.F.D. (Box A29-9B)
    - Rush, Dr. Benjamin (see also Jefferson - Papers of) (Box A29-9B)
    - Rush, N. Orwin (Box A29-9B)
    - Rush, Richard (Box A29-9B)
    - Rushton, Peters (Box A29-9B)
    - Rushton, William J. (Box A29-9B)
    - Russell County - Newspapers (Box A29-9B)
    - Russell, John J. (Box A29-9C)
    - Rutherford, John C. - Papers (Box A29-9C)
    - Rutman, Darrett B. (Box A29-9C)
    - Ryan, Father Abram J. (Box A29-9C)
    - Ryan, Thomas Fortune (Box A29-9C)
    - Ryland, Charles H. (Box A29-9C)
    - Rylands (Box A29-9C)
    - Ryskamp, John H. (Box A29-9C)
    - S Misc. 1930-1953 (Box A29-9C)
    - S Misc. 1954-1974 (Box A29-9D)
    - S Misc. 1988-1989 (Box A29-9D)
    - S Misc. 1975-1980 (Box A29-9E)
    - S Misc. 1982-1987 (Box A29-9E)
    - S.A.A. - Institutional Evaluation (Box A29-9F)
    - Sabine Hall (Box A29-9F)
    - Sadleir-Black Collection (see also Black, Robert) (Box A29-9F)
    - St. George's Parish (Box A29-9F)
    - St. John's (Box A29-9F)
    - Saint Memin (Box A29-9F)
    - Salem Virginia (Box A29-9F)
    - Sanborn, Franklin B. (Box A29-9F)
    - Sandburg, Carl (Box A29-9F)
    - Sanders, H.O. (Box A29-9F)
    - Sanders, Williams (Box A29-9F)
    - Sandys (see also Davis, Richard Beale) (Box A29-9F)
    - Sandys Family (Box A29-9F)
    - Sandys, George (Box A29-9F)
    - Santayana Collection (Box A29-9F)
    - Santayana, George (Box A29-9G)
    - Sargent, Winthrop (Box A29-9G)
    - Savage, A.D. (Box A29-9G)
    - Savage, Louise (Box A29-9G)
    - Scheide (died 1942) (Box A29-9G)
    - Schele de Vere (Box A29-9G)
    - Schlesinger, A.M. (Box A29-9G)
    - Scholarly Resources, Inc. 1989-1990 (Box A29-9G)
    - Schoolcraft, Henry R. (see also McGregor Advisory Committee) (Box A29-9G)
    - Schuman's (Box A29-9G)
    - Science Fiction (Box A29-9G)
    - Scopes, John E. (Box A29-9G)
    - Scotland - Records of (Box A29-9G)
    - Scott, Hugh (Box A29-9G)
    - Scott Collection - Exhibit and Dinner (Box A29-9G)
    - Scott, Sir Walter Raleigh (Box A29-9G)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley (Box A29-9G)
    - Scruggs, Philip Lightfoot (Box A29-9G)
    - Security Copies of Microfilm (Box A29-9G)
    - Seal - University of Virginia (Box A29-9H)
    - Seddon, James A. (Box A29-9H)
    - Seibel, Fred O. (Box A29-9H)
    - Seibel, Fred O. - Cartoons (Box A29-9H)
    - Semmes, Thomas (Box A29-9H)
    - Serials (Box A29-9H)
    - Sermons (Box A29-9H)
    - Sesquicentennial Exhibit - Manuscripts Division (Box A29-9H)
    - Sessler, Charles (Box A29-9H)
    - Settle, Mary Lee (Box A29-9H)
    - Seven Society (Box A29-9H)
    - Seven Gables Bookshop (Box A29-9H)
    - Seward Forest (Box A29-9H)
    - Shackelford Family Papers (Box A29-9H)
    - Shackelford, George Green (Box A29-9H)
    - Shackelford, George Green (Box A29-9I)
    - Shadwell (Box A29-9I)
    - Shakespeare (Box A29-9I)
    - Shakespeare - Pavier Quartos (Box A29-9I)
    - Shannon, Edgar F. (Box A29-9I)
    - Shapiro, S.R. (Box A29-9I)
    - Sharitt, J.L. (Box A29-9I)
    - Shaw, Albert (Box A29-9I)
    - Shaw, George Bernard (Box A29-9I)
    - Shea, Vincent (Box A29-9I)
    - Shelley (Box A29-9I)
    - Shelley, Fred (Box A29-9I)
    - Shelton Family (Box A29-9I)
    - Shelton, Margaret A. - MSS #10630 (Box A29-9I)
    - Shepard, Sam (Box A29-9I)
    - Shepherd, Susie V. (Box A29-9I)
    - Shepherd, Thomas (Box A29-9I)
    - Shepperson, A.B. (Box A29-9I)
    - Shipp, Barnard - Library (Box A29-9I)
    - Shirley Plantation (Box A29-9I)
    - Short, Christopher (Box A29-9J)
    - Short, William (Box A29-9J)
    - Short Title Catalogue (Box A29-9J)
    - Showalter, Jerry (Box A29-9J)
    - Siamese Twins (Box A29-9J)
    - Sign-Up Sheet - Word Processor 1984-1985 (Box A29-9J)
    - Signs (Box A29-9J)
    - Silverfish Control (Box A29-9J)
    - Silver, Rollo (Box A29-9J)
    - Silvette, Dr. Herbert (Box A29-9J)
    - Simms, William Gilmore (Box A29-9J)
    - Simpson, Robert Smith (Box A29-9J)
    - Sims, Mrs. A.W. (Box A29-9J)
    - Sinclair, Upton (Box A29-9J)
    - Sioussat, St. George L. (see also Library of congress - Manuscripts) (Box A29-9J)
    - Sitwell, Edith (Box A29-9J)
    - Sizer, Theodore (Box A29-9J)
    - Skipwith Papers (Box A29-9J)
    - Slagle, Kathryn L. (see also Cobb, Mrs. Clarence) (Box A29-9J)
    - Slaughter Family Papers / Slaughter, Jane C. / Slaughter, William A. (Box A29-9J)
    - Slavery & Slave Trade (Box A29-9K)
    - Slaughter, Capt. Philip (Box A29-9K)
    - Slemp, C. Bascom (Box A29-9K)
    - Slide Show - Manuscripts Dept. (Box A29-9K)
    - Small, Miriam R. (Box A29-9K)
    - Small, Sydney (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Charles Alphonso (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Charles W. (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Gen. Daniel (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Edmund L.R. (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Mrs. Edward Nelson (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Elizabeth Oakes (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Forrest (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Glenn Curtis (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Howard W. (Box A29-9K)
    - Smith, Howard W. (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Howard W. - Appraisal of papers (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, John (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Nellie S. (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Mrs. Edward Nelson 1985-1987 (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Peter (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Rixey (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Roy (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Russell (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Seba (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Gen. Samuel (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Snell (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Thomas Adams (see also Dictionary of American Biography) (Box A29-9L)
    - Smith, Gov. William (Box A29-9L)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box A29-9L)
    - Snavely, Tipton R. (Box A29-9L)
    - Snoddy, L.B. (Box A29-9L)
    - Society for the Propagation of the Gospel (Box A29-9L)
    - Society of American Archivists (Box A29-9L)
    - Sons of the American Revolution - Thomas Jefferson Chapter 1988 (Box A29-9L)
    - Spong, William 1988 (Box A29-9L)
    - Paper - Samples (Box A29-9M)
    - Paper - Rag Stock - Samples (Box A29-9M)
    - Society of American Archivists 1956-1981 (Box A29-9M)
    - Paper - Samples (Box A29-9M)
    - Paper - Rag Stock - Samples (Box A29-9M)
    - Society of American Archivists 1956-1981 (Box A29-9N)
    - Society of American Archivists - Committee on (Box A29-9N)
    - College...Archives (Box A29-9N)
    - Society of the Cincinnati in the State of Virginia (Box A29-9N)
    - Solar Screen Corporation (Box A29-9N)
    - Somerville, Lila (Box A29-9N)
    - Sondley Library (Box A29-9N)
    - Sons of the American Revolution 1984-1987 (Box A29-9N)
    - South Africa (Box A29-9N)
    - South American Material (Box A29-9N)
    - South Atlantic M.L.A. (Box A29-9N)
    - South Carolina (Box A29-9N)
    - South Carolina - Secession Ord. (Box A29-9N)
    - South Carolina University (Box A29-9N)
    - Southall, Dr. James P.C. (Box A29-9O)
    - Southeastern Library Association (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Books Competition (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Historical Assn. (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Historical Assn. - Journal of Southern History (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Historical Assn. - Joint Session w/ Amer. Hist. Assn. 1944 (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Historical Societies & Libraries (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Humanities Conference (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Library Service (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Railway System (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Society for Philosophy & Psychology (Box A29-9O)
    - Southern Welding & Machine Co. (Box A29-9O)
    - Southwest Virginia - Bibliography (Box A29-9O)
    - Sowerby, Millicent (Box A29-9O)
    - Spalding (Box A29-9O)
    - Spain (Box A29-9O)
    - Sparrow, Carroll Mason (Box A29-9O)
    - Special Collections Building (Box A29-9O)
    - Special Collections Building - Potential Donors (Box A29-9O)
    - Special Collections Building - Building Plans (Box A29-9O)
    - Special Collections Lib. - Correspondence (Box A29-9P)
    - Special Collections - Reports on Mss submitted to Ash's Subject (Box A29-9P)
    - Spectator (Box A29-9P)
    - Spencer, Anne (Box A29-9P)
    - Spencer Bibliography (Box A29-9P)
    - Spencer, Herbert (Box A29-9P)
    - Spilman, Louis (Box A29-9P)
    - Spivey, Herman E. (Box A29-9P)
    - Spong, William (Box A29-9P)
    - Sposito, Paul (Box A29-9P)
    - Spotswood (see also American Autograph shop; Stettinius) (Box A29-9P)
    - Springs (Box A29-9P)
    - Stamp and Coin Exhibition 1956 (Box A29-9P)
    - Stamping (Box A29-9P)
    - Stamps (Box A29-9P)
    - Stanford University Libraries (Box A29-9P)
    - Staples, Abraham P. (Box A29-9P)
    - Star of Seville (Box A29-9P)
    - State Documents (Box A29-9P)
    - State Documents - Problems (Box A29-9P)
    - Statistics - Report to Provost 1984 (Box A29-9P)
    - Stead, William Force (Box A29-9P)
    - Steadman, Rev. Melvin Lee, Jr. (Box A29-9P)
    - Stearns, Florence Dickinson (Box A29-9P)
    - Steele, Oliver (Box A29-9P)
    - Stefansson Library (Box A29-9P)
    - Steinbeck, John (Box A29-9P)
    - Stenhause, Mrs. John W. (see also Nourse) (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stephens, Alexander H. (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stephens Press (Box A29-9Q)
    - Steptoe, James (Box A29-9Q)
    - Sterling, George (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stern, Madeleine (see also Russell, John) (Box A29-9Q)
    - Sterne (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Misc. (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Completed Applications (alphabetical A - B) (Box A29-9Q)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Completed Applications (alphabetical C - R) (Box A29-9R)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Applications (alphabetical A - Z) (Box A29-9S)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Completed Applications (alphabetical S - Z) (Box A29-9T)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Misc. 1983-1987 (Box A29-9T)
    - Stettinius, E.R. - Misc. 1989 (Box A29-9T)
    - Steuben, Baron von F. (Box A29-9T)
    - Stevens, Henry, Son & Stiles (Box A29-9T)
    - Stevens, Wallace (Box A29-9T)
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box A29-9T)
    - Stevenson, Andrew (Box A29-9T)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis (Box A29-9T)
    - Stewardship (Box A29-9T)
    - Stilwell, Mrs. Joseph W. (Box A29-9T)
    - Stivers, R.E. (Box A29-9T)
    - Stocker, Arthur E. (Box A29-9T)
    - Stocking, Robert (Box A29-9T)
    - Stockton, Frank (Box A29-10A)
    - Stoddard, Charles Warren (Box A29-10A)
    - Stokes, William E. (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone, Mrs. Brandon O. (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone, Edward - Bookplate (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone, Edward - Exhibit (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone Printing & Manufacturing Co. (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone, Edward - Library (Box A29-10A)
    - Stone, Edward (Box A29-10A)
    - Stoneham, Louis H. (Box A29-10A)
    - Storm, Colton (see also american Book-Prices; Virginia - Currency) (Box A29-10A)
    - Stowe, Harriet Beecher (Box A29-10A)
    - Strauss, Herbert A. (Box A29-10A)
    - Streeter Railroad Collection 1949 (Box A29-10A)
    - Streeter, Thomas W. 1941-1967 (Box A29-10B)
    - Strickler Family (Box A29-10B)
    - Stringfellow, F.B. (Box A29-10B)
    - Strode, Aubrey (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart, Alexander H.H. (see also Stuart-Baldwin Papers) (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart, J.E.B. (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart-Baldwin Papers (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart Family Papers (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart Hall Library (Box A29-10B)
    - Stuart, Mr. & Mrs. William A. (Box A29-10B)
    - Stubbs, Kendon L. (Box A29-10B)
    - Student Assistants (Box A29-10B)
    - Student Assistants - Payroll (Box A29-10B)
    - Suffolk Virginia (Box A29-10B)
    - Sully (Box A29-10B)
    - Summers, Andrew R. (Box A29-10B)
    - Summers Family Papers (Box A29-10C)
    - Summers, Lewis Preston (Box A29-10C)
    - Supergirls / Jessup, Claudia (Box A29-10C)
    - Superscope Library of the Spoken Word (Box A29-10C)
    - Supervisory Development Plan (Box A29-10C)
    - Supplies (Box A29-10C)
    - Supreme Court (Box A29-10C)
    - Surplus Property - Sale of 1980-1981 (Box A29-10C)
    - Swan Papers (Box A29-10C)
    - Swanson, Claude (Box A29-10C)
    - Sweeney, William B. (Box A29-10C)
    - Sweet Briar (Box A29-10C)
    - Sweden (Box A29-10C)
    - Swem, Earl Gregg, Library (Box A29-10C)
    - Swinburne (Box A29-10C)
    - Switzer, G. Fred / Applications (see also Byrd - Applications) (Box A29-10C)
    - Syme, Ronald (Box A29-10C)
    - Symons, Arthur (Box A29-10C)
    - T misc. c. 1933-1967 (Box A29-10D)
    - T misc. 1940-1989 (Box A29-10D)
    - Talbot Family / Bible (Box A29-10D)
    - Talbott, Frank, Jr. (Box A29-10D)
    - Talley, Mrs. E.A. (Mabel) (Box A29-10D)
    - Tanasoca, Donald (Box A29-10D)
    - Tape Recorder (Box A29-10D)
    - Tarkington, Booth (Box A29-10E)
    - Tarleton (Box A29-10E)
    - Tate, Allen (Box A29-10E)
    - Tate, Vernon D. (Box A29-10E)
    - Taverns (Box A29-10E)
    - Tax & Tax Reform Act (Box A29-10E)
    - Tayloe Family Papers (Box A29-10E)
    - Tayloe Papers (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Charles Elisha (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Creed (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor Family Papers (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, George K. (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Harry B. (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Henry (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Henry C. (see also Rolfe, John) (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Henry M. (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Olivia A. (see also Edgehill-Randolph Papers / MSS #8682) (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Olivia #1 (see also MSS #5533) (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, Olivia #2 (see also MSS #8937) (Box A29-10E)
    - Taylor, John (of Caroline) (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Mary P. (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Maxwell D. (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Olivia A. / Edgehill-Randolph Papers (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Peter (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Raleigh (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Richard P. (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Robert H. (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Robert G. (Box A29-10F)
    - Taylor, Tazewell (Box A29-10F)
    - Tazewell Family Papers (Box A29-10G)
    - Tazewell, John P. (see also MSS #10009) (Box A29-10G)
    - Tekes, Captain (see also Phillips, Horace E.) (Box A29-10G)
    - Telephones (Box A29-10G)
    - Telephone Bills 1990-1991 (Box A29-10G)
    - Television Archives (Box A29-10G)
    - Temperature & Humidity Records (Box A29-10G)
    - Tennessee Archives (Box A29-10G)
    - Tennessee Imprints & Copyrights etc. (Box A29-10G)
    - Tennis, Le Grand (Box A29-)
    - Tennyson, Alfred Lord (Box A29-10G)
    - Terrell-Carr Family Papers (Box A29-10G)
    - Tetley, Gerard (Box A29-10G)
    - Thank-you's 1988-1989 (Box A29-10H)
    - Tucker-Smith-Harrison Papers (Box A29-10H)
    - Tunstall, Robert B. 1930-1955 (Box A29-10H)
    - Tunstall, Mrs. Robert B. (Box A29-10H)
    - Tunstall Bequest 1988-1989 (Box A29-10H)
    - Turnbull, Robert J. (see also Jackson, Stuart) (Box A29-10H)
    - Turner, Charles W. (Box A29-10H)
    - Turner, Fleming (Box A29-10H)
    - Turner, Nancy Byrd (Box A29-10H)
    - Turner, Nat (Box A29-10H)
    - Turpin, Edna (Box A29-10H)
    - Tusing, Henry (Box A29-10H)
    - Tuttle, Stephen (Box A29-10H)
    - Tutwiler, Henry (Box A29-10H)
    - Twin Oaks Community (Box A29-10H)
    - Twyman Family Papers (Box A29-10H)
    - Tyler, James Hoge (Box A29-10H)
    - Tyler, Pres. John (Box A29-10H)
    - John Tyler Peace Conference (Box A29-10H)
    - Tyler, Lyon G. (Box A29-10H)
    - Thackeray, William M. (Box A29-10I)
    - Thalhimer, Morton G. (Box A29-10I)
    - Thank-you's 1974-1984 (Box A29-10I)
    - Theft - Memorial Hall 1981 (Box A29-10I)
    - Theft - Lists of Missing Items (Box A29-10I)
    - Theses & Dissertations 1982-1984 (Box A29-10I)
    - Theses & Dissertations 1961-1981 (Box A29-10J)
    - Theses & Dissertations - Procedure 1969 (Box A29-10J)
    - Theses & Dissertations n.d. (Box A29-10J)
    - Theses & Dissertations 1986-1989 (Box A29-10J)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Exhibit etc. (Box A29-10K)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (Box A29-10K)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Fund Records (Box A29-10K)
    - Thomas, Alsen Franklin (Box A29-10K)
    - Thomas, Dylan (Box A29-10K)
    - Thomas, William H.B. (Box A29-10K)
    - Thompson, Edwin A. (Box A29-10K)
    - Thompson, Mrs. John Ford (Box A29-10K)
    - Thompson, John Reuben (Box A29-10L)
    - Thompson, Lawrence (Box A29-10L)
    - Thompson, Maurice (Box A29-10L)
    - Thoreau, Henry David (Box A29-10L)
    - Thornton Map (see also Verner, Coolie) (Box A29-10L)
    - Thompson, Randall (Box A29-10L)
    - Thornton, William (Box A29-10L)
    - Thorup, Oscar A. (Box A29-10L)
    - Thurber, James (Box A29-10L)
    - Thurlow, Constance E. 1950 (Box A29-10L)
    - Tiddeman, Mark (Box A29-10L)
    - Timberlake Family (Box A29-10L)
    - Tinker / Tinker, William (Box A29-10M)
    - Tobacco (Box A29-10M)
    - Todd Family (Box A29-10M)
    - Toddsbury (Box A29-10M)
    - Toklas, Alice B. (Box A29-10M)
    - Toler, Mrs. John M. (Box A29-10M)
    - Toole, John (Box A29-10M)
    - Toole, Jon (Box A29-10M)
    - Torrence, Clayton (Box A29-10M)
    - Tours (Box A29-10M)
    - Towles Family Papers (Box A29-10M)
    - Townes, S. Halcott (Box A29-10M)
    - Toy, Crawford Howell (Box A29-10M)
    - Transmittal Forms - Completed 1981-1984 (Box A29-10M)
    - Transmittal Forms 1987-1991 (Box A29-10M)
    - Transmittals 1990 (Box A29-10M)
    - Transmittal Forms 1985-1986 (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Clendenning (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Lindemann (Box A29-10N)
    - Transportation of Poor to Virginia (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Berkeley (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Cole (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Freudenberg (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Hull (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Johnson (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Jordan (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Kern (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - McGehee (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Plunkett (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Smith (Box A29-10N)
    - Travel Vouchers - Tanner (Box A29-10O)
    - Trigg, Mrs.William (Box A29-10O)
    - Trimble, Kelly (Box A29-10O)
    - Trist, Nicholas Philip (Box A29-10O)
    - Trist, Nicholas 1988 (Box A29-10O)
    - Trollope, Anthony (Box A29-10O)
    - Trout, Dr. Hugh H. (Box A29-10O)
    - Trout, P.H. (Box A29-10O)
    - Trudeau, Gary (Box A29-10O)
    - Truman, Harry S. (Box A29-10O)
    - Tuck, William M. (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker, Bishop Beverley (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker Family (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker, George (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker, Henry St. George (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker, J.B. (Box A29-10O)
    - Tucker, Nathaniel B. (Box A29-10O)
    - U Misc. 1940-1989 (Box A29-10P)
    - Ulster County Gazette (Box A29-10P)
    - Underwood Family Papers (Box A29-10P)
    - Union League (Box A29-10P)
    - University of Virginia - Alumni Association 1989-1990 (Box A29-10P)
    - University of Virginia - Photos 1989 (Box A29-10P)
    - United Book Display (Box A29-10P)
    - U.S. - Senate (Box A29-10P)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy (Box A29-10P)
    - United Virginia Bank - Records - Richmond (Box A29-10P)
    - University Microfilms 1961-1969 (Box A29-10P)
    - University Microfilms - Shipping Notices (Box A29-10P)
    - University Publications of America 1986-1988 (Box A29-10P)
    - University of Virginia - Misc. (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Alumni Association (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Archives & Records (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Art Objects - Inventory (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Photos & Prints 1985-1987 (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Board of Visitors (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Board of Visitors - Minutes Index (Box A29-10Q)
    - University of Virginia - Brooks Museum (Box A29-10R)